Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 353.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Answers concerning the United Steelworkers of America, 1974; Publication (Box 353.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: By the workers for the workers, Publication (Box 353.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Material for speeches or interviews, Publication (Box 353.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: The union is You! A guide for USA-CIO grievance committeemen, Publication (Box 353.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: The union is you!: the grievanceman's handbook, 1960; Publication (Box 353.1, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Toward equitable income distribution; some social and economic considerations for union wage policy., 1966; Publication (Box 353.1, Folder 3)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 353.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Detailed analysis of the industry proposal of Nov. 15 and the Kaiser Settlement, 1960; Publication (Box 353.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Public relations for local unions, 1974; Publication (Box 353.1, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Training workers in the steel industry, Publication (Box 353.1, Folder 4)
    Notes: A manual for staff representatives and local union officers dealing with the setting-up and the administering of an apprenticeship training program. 2 copies
  - Item 4: Why won't the big steel companies accept the Kaiser pattern for lasting industrial peace?, 1960; Publication (Box 353.1, Folder 4)
    Notes: Steelworkers' agreement with Kaiser may forever end conflict in steel: read what Edgar Kaiser says about this historic union contract.
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 353.1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Report on International Election, 1946; Publication (Box 353.1, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Final report, delegates seated to date by the Credential Committee, 1946; Publication (Box 353.1, Folder 5)
    Author: Committee on Credentials
    Notes: May 18, 1946, Third Constitutional Convention of the Unied Steelworkers of America.
  - Item 3: Partial report of the Credentials Committee, 1952; Publication (Box 353.1, Folder 5)
    Notes: Sixth Constitutional Convention of the United Steelworkers of America: Convention Hall, Philadelphia, Pa., May 13, 1952.
  - Item 4: Partial report, delegates seated to date by the Credential Committee, 1946; Publication (Box 353.1, Folder 5)
    Notes: May 14, 1946, Third Constitutional Convention of the Unied Steel-workers of America.
  - Item 5: Report of the Committee on Resolutions, 1952; Publication (Box 353.1, Folder 5)
    Author: Committee on Resolutions
    Notes: Sixth Constitutional Convention of the United Steelworkers of America, Convention Hall, Philadelphia, Pa. 2 copies
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 353.1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: A special report on your Union's programs for employment and income security, 1964; Publication (Box 353.1, Folder 6)
    Notes: Twelfth Constitutional Convention, United Steelworkers of America, Atlantic City, New Jersey, Sept., 1964.
  - Item 2: Economic factors relating to wage negotiations in the steel industry for 1947, Publication (Box 353.1, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Facts on steel: profits, productivity, prices and wages, 1956, Publication (Box 353.1, Folder 6)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 354, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Labors interest in financial information, 1948; Publication (Box 354, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Correspondence - [letter accompanying a pamphlet - "an income and expenditure study for January, 1945..", Publication (Box 354, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Five years of war profits, 1940-1944, compared to five years peace-time profits, 1935-1939, 1945; Publication (Box 354, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Steel profits, 1936 thru 1943: four war years 1940-1943, compared to four peace year, 1936-1939, 1944; Publication (Box 354, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Steelworkers need a $2.00-a-day wage increase, 1946; Publication (Box 354, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: The Braddock steelworker, 1945; Publication (Box 354, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Wages-prices-profits in the steel industry, 1949; Publication (Box 354, Folder 1)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 354, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Re: Major contract economic gains - US Steel Corp. - Basic contracts - (1937-1952) (Box 354, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: The Recent Steel price increases: an analytical statement., 1950; Publication (Box 354, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Re: interpreting the provisions of the pension agreements, 1950; Publication (Box 354, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Re: United States Steel Corporation, 1953 and Fourth Quarter financial summary, 1954; Publication (Box 354, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Re: Steel industry profits - 1953, Publication (Box 354, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Re: Steel industry profits - 1954, Publication (Box 354, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Re: Steel industry profits - 1958, Publication (Box 354, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Re: A survey of the minimum rate and increment differentials in the steelworker., 1952; Publication (Box 354, Folder 2)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 354, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Higher wages and the national economy, 1959; Publication (Box 354, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Report on certain "fringe" provisions in major contracts in industries other than basic steel, 1959; Publication (Box 354, Folder 3)
    Author: Research Department
  - Item 3: 1957 and Fourth Quarter Financial Summary (United States Steel Corporation), Publication (Box 354, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: 1958 and Fourth Quarter Financial Summary (United States Steel Corporation), Publication (Box 354, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Negotiated wage rate increases of major companies and union, 1956; Publication (Box 354, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: 1955 and Fourth Quarter Financial Summary (United States Steel Corporation), Publication (Box 354, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Memorandum No. 9, 1956; Publication (Box 354, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: 1956 and Fourth Quarter Financial Summary (United States Steel Corporation), Publication (Box 354, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Steel Industry Profits - 1956, Publication (Box 354, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: 1954 and Fourth Quarter Financial Summary (United States Steel Corporation), Publication (Box 354, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Steel Industry Profits - 1955, Publication (Box 354, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Re: Salaries and other financial rewards to Executives of Basic Steel Companies in 1956, Publication (Box 354, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: An economic documentation of the steelowrkers' position in the 1959 steel strike, Publication (Box 354, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Long-term employment trends in the Basic Steel Industry, 1959; Publication (Box 354, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: Foreign competition and steel wages, 1959; Publication (Box 354, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: Re: Survey of certain "fringe" benefits in Major collective bargaining agreements, 1959; Publication (Box 354, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: Why a steel price increase in 1957?, Publication (Box 354, Folder 3)
    Notes: Statement by David J. McDonald .. and a presentation by Otis Brubaker
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 354, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: An economic documentation of the steelowrkers' position in the 1959 steel strike, Publication (Box 354, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: The Recent Steel price increases: an analytical statement., 1950; Publication (Box 354, Folder 4)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 354, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Steel industry profits - 1955, Publication (Box 354, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Steel indusry profits - 1957, Publication (Box 354, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: The minimum rate and increment differentials in Steelworker-organized plants of companies, 1955; Publication (Box 354, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Minimum rate and increment differentials after the 1958 wage increase, Publication (Box 354, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Report on certain "fringe" provisions in major contracts in industries other than basic steel, 1959; Publication (Box 354, Folder 5)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 355, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: USWA safety and health program, 1973; Publication (Box 355, Folder 1)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 355, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: A survey of steelworker-organized companies in the valves and fittings industry and the pumps and compressors industry, 1966; Publication (Box 355, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Re: Executive salaries in the basic steel industry - 1962, Publication (Box 355, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Re: Cost of living and other wage changes since the last steel wage increase, 1963; Publication (Box 355, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Re: Steel industry profits - 1963 - Third quarter and first nine months financial survey, Publication (Box 355, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Cumulative negotiated wage increases, 1961; Publication (Box 355, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Steel industry profits - First quarter 1963, Publication (Box 355, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: United States Steel Corporation - 1963 - Second quarter financial survey, Publication (Box 355, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: A comparative study of lithograph unit wages and 'fringes' in American Can Co. in Steelworker and Lithographer & Photoengraver agreements, 1965; Publication (Box 355, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Salaries and other financial rewards to executives of Aluminum and can companies - 1959, Publication (Box 355, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Brief union summary of the 1967 copper strike, Publication (Box 355, Folder 2)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 355, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Re: Liberalization of depreciation allowance, 1961; Publication (Box 355, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Re: Significance of the discontinuation of the steel operating rate by AISI, 1961; Publication (Box 355, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Cumulative earnings gains of average steelworkers, 1960-1962 (Box 355, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Re: United States Steel Corporation - 1959 and Fourth Quarter Financial Summary, Publication (Box 355, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Comments by Otis BrubakerBefore the steel hearings of the Joint Economic Committee, 1963; Publication (Box 355, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Re: Salaries and other financial rewards to executives of basic steel companies, 1959, Publication (Box 355, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Re: United States Steel Corporation - 1963 and First Quarter Financial Summary, Publication (Box 355, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Re: United States Steel Corporation - 1962 Annual and Fourth Quarter Financial Summary, Publication (Box 355, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Steel industry profits - first half 1963, Publication (Box 355, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Steel industry profits - 1962 - Full year and quarterly data, Publication (Box 355, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Comments on the labor department study entitled "Collective bargaining in the basic steel industry", 1961; Publication (Box 355, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Steel industry profits - 1959 - Full year and quarterly data, Publication (Box 355, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Severance and transition arrangements in the European coal and steel community, 1961; Publication (Box 355, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Notes for the 1961 meeting of the local union presidents of Continental Can Company, Inc., Publication (Box 355, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: A comparative study of lithograph unit wages and fringes in continental Can Co., Inc. in Steelworker and Lithographer & Photoengraver agreements, 1965; Publication (Box 355, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: Brief union summary of the 1967 copper strike, Publication (Box 355, Folder 3)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 355, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: A speech delivered by Clinton S. Golden, 1959; Publication (Box 355, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, local union services available to retirees and older workers, 1958; Publication (Box 355, Folder 5)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 355, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Senior Steelworker, 1963; Publication (Box 355, Folder 6)
    Notes: no. 1-13 (1963)
  - Item 2: The Senior Steelworker, 1964; Publication (Box 355, Folder 6)
    Notes: no. 14 (1964)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 355, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Bargaining for pay equity, 1990; Publication (Box 355, Folder 7)
    Author: National Committee on Pay Equity
  - Item 2: letter about 'strong progressive labor movement', 1976; Publication (Box 355, Folder 7)
    Author: Victor Reuther
  - Item 3: letter introducing "Ed Sadlowski", 1976; Publication (Box 355, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Report of the wage rate inequities committee, 1946; Publication (Box 355, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: Sadlowski gets boost from 2 slate victories, 1976; Publication (Box 355, Folder 7)
    Notes: Newspaper clipping
- International Stereotypers' and Electrotypers' Union of North America, Publication (Box 356, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Correspondence - letter about voting for President of the USA, 1968; Publication (Box 356, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Sove the problemvote for Humphrey, 1968; Publication (Box 356, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Wage rates and fringe benefits under contracts with locals (spread sheets), 1954; Publication (Box 356, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Official Ballot, 1935; Publication (Box 356, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Spread of work plan, 1931; Publication (Box 356, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Digest of minutes Atlanta meeting, 1920; Publication (Box 356, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Wage scales of subordinate unions (July, 1928), Publication (Box 356, Folder 1)
- International Stereotypers' and Electrotypers' Union of North America, Publication (Box 356, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Re: merger proposition which will be voted on -, 1966; Publication (Box 356, Folder 2)
    Notes: Correspondence
  - Item 2: Newspaper Stereotypers' scale of wages as of July, 1965, Publication (Box 356, Folder 2)
- United Stone and Allied Products Workers of America, Publication (Box 356, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: In the matter of arbitration between Petoskey Portland Cement Company and United Stone and Allied Products Workers of America, 1949- 1950 (Box 356, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Notes for the 1961 meeting of the local union presidents of Continental Can Company, Inc., 1952; Publication (Box 356, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Your Paper, 1949; Publication (Box 356, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 3, no. 2 (1949)
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, Publication (Box 357, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Award of the Board of Arbitration: between: Springfield Street Railway Company, Worcester Consolidated Street Railway Company, Milford, Attleboro & Woonsocket Street Railway Company, Interstate Consolidated Street Railway Company, Attleboro Branch Railroa, 1922; Publication (Box 357, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: In the matter of arbitration between Div. 241 of the Amalgamated Assoc. of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employes of America and Chicago Transit Authority, 1953; Publication (Box 357, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: In the matter of arbitration between Triboro Coach Corporation and Division No. 1104, Amalgamated Assoc. of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, 1939; Publication (Box 357, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: In the matter of the arbitration between Cincinnati Transit Company and Division 627, Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, AFL-CIO: final opinion and award of Board of Arbitration, October 7, 1957, Publication (Box 357, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: In the matter of the arbitration between Triboro Coach Corporation and Division 1104, Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, AFL-CIO: preliminary statement, 1939; Publication (Box 357, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: In the matter of the arbitration between United Traction Company (Albany, New York) and Division 1321, Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, 1957; Publication (Box 357, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Opinion of the Chairman: In the matter of the arbitration between Capital Transit Company and Division 689, Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, A.F.L., 1947; Publication (Box 357, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, Publication (Box 357, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: In the matter of the petition of the Amalgamated Association of Street and Electric Railway Employes of America, Division no. 578 to the Industrial Commission of Wisconsin, for an adjustment of its differences with the Milwaukee Electric Railway and Light, 1912; Publication (Box 357, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: In the matter of arbitration between Trustees for Pittsburgh (PA.) Railways Co. and for Pittsburgh (PA.) Mortor Coach Co. and the Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, Division No. 85 and 1084: Award...., 1950; Publication (Box 357, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Findings of the Board of Arbitration, acting by virtue and under authority of a certain agreement between the Cincinnati Traction Company and its Employes, dated May 19, 1913, Publication (Box 357, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: In the matter of arbitration between Pittsburgh (PA.) Railways Co. and the Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, Division No. 85 and 1084, 1951; Publication (Box 357, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: In the matter of arbitration between Trustees for Pittsburgh (PA.) Railways Co. and for Pittsburgh (PA.) Mortor Coach Co. and the Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, Division No. 85 and 1084, 1950; Publication (Box 357, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: In the matter of the controversy between the Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America and the Albany Southern Railroad Company, regarding the interpretation and application of Rule 37 of the Agreement entere, 1912; Publication (Box 357, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Opinion of the Chairman: In the matter of the arbitration between Capital Transit Company and Division 689, Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, A.F.L., 1947; Publication (Box 357, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, Publication (Box 357, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: This is an explanation of your retirement plan, 1960; Publication (Box 357, Folder 3)
    Author: Local 1005
  - Item 2: Supreme Court - Oct. Term 1951, Publication (Box 357, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Wage history of the Amalgamated association of street and electric railway employes of America, November 1, 1914., Publication (Box 357, Folder 3)
    Author: Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America
  - Item 4: Brooklyn Trolley Strike, 1895; Publication (Box 357, Folder 3)
    Notes: Newspaper clipping - VERY brittle
  - Item 5: Wages of the Motormen and Conductors who are members of the Amalgamated Association of Street and Electric Railway Employes of America, 1916; Publication (Box 357, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: The Union Leader, 1923; Publication (Box 357, Folder 3)
    Notes: Vol. 24, no. 43 (1923)
  - Item 7: The Traction Workers' Bulletin, 1926; Publication (Box 357, Folder 3)
    Notes: Vol. 1, no. 2 (1926). 2 copies
  - Item 8: Employees Retirement Plan, 1958; Publication (Box 357, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, Publication (Box 357, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Local Division Directory (1956-1962) (Box 357, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, Publication (Box 357, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Brief in behalf of divisions, 1919; Publication (Box 357, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Argument before the Committee on Legal Affairs of the massachusetts Legislature, 1919; Publication (Box 357, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, Publication (Box 357, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Trainmen trounced on S.E. Greyhound, Publication (Box 357, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Golden Jubilee of the., 1942; Publication (Box 357, Folder 6)
    Notes: Program
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, Publication (Box 357, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: A contemporary analysis of labor union; development, structure, functions: Amalgamed Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employes of America. (AFL-CIO-CLC), 1962; Publication (Box 357, Folder 7)
    Author: Miles E. Hoffman
  - Item 2: A refresher course in labor relations, Publication (Box 357, Folder 7)
    Author: Moses Shapiro
    Notes: Fort Pitt Hotel - English Room
  - Item 3: A California outrage: the Los Angeles story, 1960; Publication (Box 357, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: United States District Court for the Northern District of Oklahoma: Civil No. 5429: Division No. 892, Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, AFL-CIO, Complainant -v- M. K. & O. Transit Lines, Inc., Defend, Publication (Box 357, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Association of Street, Electric Railway and Motor Coach Employees of America, Publication (Box 357, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Financial statement, 1963; Publication (Box 357, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Report of the General Executive Board to the thirty-seventh convention, 1963; Publication (Box 357, Folder 8)
- SDS (Students for a Democratic Society (U.S.)), Publication (Box 358, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Wanted for exploitation racism and murder! Columbia. The Boss, Publication (Box 358, Folder 1)
    Notes: Newspaper
  - Item 2: SDS Convetion - Chicago Colliseum (Confidential), 1969; Publication (Box 358, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: SDS Bulletin, 1962-1963 (Box 358, Folder 1)
    Notes: no. 3, 1962-63
  - Item 4: Revolution in Mississippi, 1962; Publication (Box 358, Folder 1)
    Author: Tom Hayden
  - Item 5: The Port Huron Statement, 1964; Publication (Box 358, Folder 1)
    Author: SDS (Students for a Democratic Society (U.S.))
- International Council of Sugar Workers and Allied Industries Unions, Publication (Box 358, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: History of the organization of Sugar Worker Unions and the growth of the International Council of Sugar Workers and allied Industries Unions, 1958; Publication (Box 358, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: LID Summer School Announcement, 1935; Publication (Box 358, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Distribution of income in the United States, 1955; Publication (Box 358, Folder 2)
    Author: Gabriel Kolko
  - Item 4: How to keep the records of your Federal labor union as outlined at the School of Instruction, 1949; Publication (Box 358, Folder 2)
    Notes: Held by the International Council of Sugar Workers and Allied Industries Unions, Denver, Colorado, June 1949.
- Tapestry Carpet Workers' Union, Publication (Box 358, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Sugar Strikers resume, 1948-1949 (Box 358, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Puerto Rico mills shut, 1948-1949 (Box 358, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Tapestry WeaversNew Shop and Union Rules (1925), Publication (Box 358, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Special Convention, Proceedings of the Law and Audit Committee J.T.U. of A., 1928; Publication (Box 358, Folder 3)
- AFT (American Federation of Teachers), Publication (Box 359, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Address by Pres. Charles Cogen to the 49th Annual Convention, 1965; Publication (Box 359, Folder 1)
    Author: Charles Cogen
  - Item 2: Summer opportunity centers - address by Vice President Humphrey, 1967; Publication (Box 359, Folder 1)
    Author: Hubert H. Humphrey
  - Item 3: Labor's part in American education, 1938; Publication (Box 359, Folder 1)
    Author: George Googe
  - Item 4: American Federation of Teachers Convention, 1940; Publication (Box 359, Folder 1)
    Author: George S. Counts